hicoool.net 2011-12-26

# High Help In Medicine And Forex » Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for  

At [HiCoool.Net](http://hicoool.net/) , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This  
privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received  
and collected by [HiCoool.Net](http://hicoool.net/) and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers, [HiCoool.Net](http://hicoool.net/) use log files. This includes  
internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (  
ISP ), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of  
clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the  
aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP  
addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.   

**Google’s search box**

Has been providing search box on this web site (the "search  
box") by Google Inc ( "Google"). You acknowledge and agree to apply privacy  
policy Google (Located on [  
http://www.google.com/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)) for using the "search box" and using the  
"search box" Google granted approval to use your personal data in accordance  
with the Privacy Policy

**Cookies and Web Beacons**   
[HiCoool.Net](http://hicoool.net/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences,  
record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit,  
customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information  
that the visitor sends. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.  
Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, . 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to  
your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on  
[HiCoool.Net](http://hicoool.net/). They  
automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other  
technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) to measure the  
effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content  
you see.   
[HiCoool.Net](http://hicoool.net/) has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given  
permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad  
servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for  
instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices.  
[  
http://www.google.com/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/privacy.html) privacy  
policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other  
advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser  
options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web  
browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy  
policy, please feel free to contact us by email at  
[Admin@HiCoool.Net](mailto:Admin@HiCoool.Net).   

**Team preparation :**
